- id: ckw-l02-955
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - エネルギー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-992
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - タイプ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1008
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ドル
  hint: "noun/counter"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1022
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - アップ
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1036
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - イメージ
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1055
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - センチメートル
  hint: "noun/counter"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1073
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - スポーツ
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1082
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - パソコン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1097
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - モデル
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1107
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - レベル
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1132
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - カード
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1137
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - チーム
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1145
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - バス
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1175
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ソフト
  hint: "noun (な-adj)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l02-1190
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ファイル
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []
